{
    "subject": "resource/Paulo_Moura",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/S\u00e3o_Jos\u00e9_do_Rio_Preto",
    "human_readable": "Paulo Moura was born in S\u00e3o Jos\u00e9 do Rio Preto.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8771253228187561,
            "question": "Name the city where Paulo Moura was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8691469430923462,
            "question": "Where was Paulo Moura born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7992331385612488,
            "question": "In what year was Paulo Moura born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6488561630249023,
            "question": "Where did Paulo Moura grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5619616508483887,
            "question": "What is Paulo Moura known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48116061091423035,
            "question": "What is Paulo Moura's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3825874328613281,
            "question": "What are some of Paulo Moura's interests?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3672105371952057,
            "question": "Does Paulo Moura have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3449271023273468,
            "question": "Does Paulo Moura have any children?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26248908042907715,
            "question": "Is Paulo Moura married?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paulo Moura was born in S\u00e3o Jos\u00e9 do Rio Preto.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6895_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Paulo Moura have any children?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6895_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Paulo Moura have any siblings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6895_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Paulo Moura's interests?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6895_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6895_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6895_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6895_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6895_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6895_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6895_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6895_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6895_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6895_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6895_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently state that Paulo Moura was born in S\u00e3o Jos\u00e9 do Rio Preto, S\u00e3o Paulo state. Therefore, the query \"Paulo Moura was born in S\u00e3o Jos\u00e9 do Rio Preto\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}